And people didn't want to hire me
because I had no experience,
this is where Pereirão from theiro's workshop is born.
Debora always faces life with great sweetness
and a smile on your face.
There are people I've been picking up as soon as I arrive
approached,
that they so detonated,
so with a drooping countenance,
so full of trouble and I managed to get a smile out of it,
no matter how disguised it is.
And a smile is much different from smiling with you.
and laugh at you.
Before I started home,
my heaven God must administer John's probe.
Maria also has these problems
because I can't take it anymore because I'm already tired.
And as Pereiram was different,
he made me 1 totally happy woman.